MERT YİĞİTTOP

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+90 538 043 11 33

yigittopm@hotmail.com

linkedin/mertyigittop

github/yigittopm

Bursa, Turkey

EXPERTISE

- Golang
- Node.js (Express.js, Nest.js)
- · React.is
- Typescript
- HTML5/CSS3/Javascript
- PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Rest, Graphql
- Docker, Kubernetes
- · AWS, Google Cloud
- Java, Spring Boot
- Design Patterns
- TDD

CERTIFICATES

Paribu Blockchain Fundamentals

Organization: Paribu ID: 66704654211627 Date: 2/2024

Amazon Web Services

Organization: BTK Akademi ID: Ko9fLZeXMM

Date: 9/2023

Google Cloud

Organization: BTK Akademi

ID: EoPfbEgOyY Date: 5/2024

SUMMARY

I am a computer engineer with more than three years of experience in software development. I have a strong knowledge of modern programming languages such as Javascript, Typescript and Golang. I have extensive front-end and back-end experience and solution-orientated development skills. My habit of constantly reading open source code, blogs and articles allows me to keep up to date with current developments in the industry and keep my knowledge up to date. I want to build the future web and money. For this, I am developing myself on Web3 and Blockchain.

EDUCATION

• Namik Kemal University | Computer Engineering 2018/2019

• Kutahya Dumlupinar University | Computer Engineering | 3.05/4 2019/2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

MakasAppFebruary 2021 to September 2021 (7 months)

Nodejs, Expressjs, TypeScript, Reactjs, Graphql, Postgresql

- Customer Management And Organization
- Application Electronic Business Card

Full Stack Developer

ITU Markalaşma Zirvesi October 2021 to December 2021 (2 months)

Nodejs, Expressjs, TypeScript, Reactjs, Graphql, Postgresql

• ITU Branding Summit Registration Form

Full Stack Developer

Konsorsiyum

July 2022 to currently

Reactjs, Nodejs, Spring Boot, Postgresql, AWS, Google Cloud

- Individual Carbon Footprint Calculation Application
- Sustainability Studies of Companies Application
- Corporate Carbon Footprint Calculation Application

OPEN SOURCE

• <u>Ethereum Organizational Website</u> | <u>Repository</u> | <u>#12083</u>

2/2024